Inventory of the Powell Family Papers 1775-1927
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Diaries, Record Books and Miscellaneous Volumes, 1861-1879., 4 items. (Box 7)
  - Record book of Rev. Sewell Stavely Hepburn, Loudoun County, Virginia, and Kent County, Maryland, (1869-1879)., 107 pages. Xcy included of pages concerning members of Powell Family. MsV4. (Box 7)
    Includes visiting, baptismal and confirmation lists, and marriages performed, accounts and prayers.